kagoo.co.uk 2015-11-30

# Privacy Policy - Kagoo

It is important that we store personal information about you so that we can provide you with the best possible experience on Kagoo.co.uk. We promise to keep your personal information private. This means:

  * We will take all reasonable steps to keep your personal information secure.
  * We won't reveal your personal information to other users of the site unless you specifically ask us to.
  * We won't give or sell any of your personal information to another company.

We store all of the data that you enter within Kagoo.co.uk including your personal name, address and contact details. We also store all of your advert related information.

We do not store any of your financial details, including your credit card or payment details.

We do not provide your personal email address or telephone number to other users of the site unless you specifically ask us to or include it in your advert text.

### 1 General

1.1 Kagoo.co.uk is a web site of Kagoo Ltd ("We", "our" and "us" in this Internet Privacy Policy). By using this site ("the web site"), you agree to the Internet Privacy Policy set out below. The Internet Privacy Policy relates to the collection and use of personal information you may supply to us through your conduct on the web site.

1.2 When you provide personal information to the web site, the Data Controller is Kagoo Ltd, the registered address for which is 13 St Donatt's Road, London, SE14 6NU.

1.3 We reserve the right, at our discretion, to modify or remove portions of this Internet Privacy Policy at any time. This Internet Privacy Policy is in addition to any other terms and conditions applicable to the web site. We do not make any representations about third party web sites that may be linked to the web site. 

1.4 We recognise the importance of protecting the privacy of information collected about visitors to our sites, in particular information that is capable of identifying an individual ("personal information"). This Internet Privacy Policy governs the manner in which your personal information, obtained through the web site, will be dealt with. This Internet Privacy Policy should be reviewed periodically so that you are updated on any changes.

### 2 Personal information

2.1 Personal information about visitors to our sites is collected only when knowingly and voluntarily submitted. For example, we may need to collect such information to provide you with further services or to answer or forward any requests or enquiries. It is our intention that this policy will protect your personal information from being dealt with in any way that is inconsistent with applicable privacy laws in the United Kingdom. 

### 3 Use of information

3.1 Our Data Controller will use your information together with other information for administration (including providing any goods, services or information you have requested), marketing, customer services and profiling your preferences. We will disclose your information to our service providers and agents solely for these purposes.

3.2 If you wish to opt out of receiving any marketing materials from us or our service providers and agents, you may unsubscribe at any time from our communications by emailing info[at]kagoo.com 

3.3 Copies of correspondence sent from the web site, that may contain personal information, are stored as archives for record-keeping and back-up purposes only. We may keep your information for a reasonable period.

3.4 You should be aware that providing information to a third party user of site such as a landlord, tenant or an agent through our web site will result in the information being passed to the third party and your information will then be held subject to the privacy obligations of that third party which may not conform with this Internet Privacy Policy.

### 4 Disclosure

4.1 Apart from where you have consented or disclosure is necessary to achieve the purpose for which it was submitted, personal information may be disclosed in special situations where we have reason to believe that doing so is necessary to identify, contact or bring legal action against anyone damaging, injuring, or interfering (intentionally or unintentionally) with our rights or property, users, or anyone else who could be harmed by such activities. Also, we may disclose personal information when we believe in good faith that the law requires disclosure.

4.2 We may engage third parties to provide you with goods or services on our behalf. In that circumstance, we may disclose your personal information to those third parties in order to meet your request for goods or services.

### 5 Security

5.1 We strive to ensure the security, integrity and privacy of personal information submitted to our sites, and we review and update our security measures in light of current technologies. Unfortunately, no data transmission over the Internet can be guaranteed to be totally secure. 

5.2 However, we will endeavour to take reasonable steps to protect the personal information you may transmit to us or from our online products and services. Once we do receive your transmission, we will also use reasonable steps to ensure its security on our systems.

5.3 In addition, our employees and the contractors who provide services related to our information systems are obliged to respect the confidentiality of any personal information held by us. However, we are not responsible for events arising from unauthorised access to your personal information.

5.4 We will endeavour to take all reasonable steps to keep accurate and up to date any information which we hold about you. If, at any time, you discover that information held about you is incorrect, you should contact us to have the information corrected.

### 6 Cookies

6.1 Cookies are data that a web site transfers to an individual's hard drive for record-keeping purposes. Cookies, which are industry standard and are used by most web sites, including those operated by us, can facilitate a user's ongoing access to and use of a site. They allow us to customise the web site to your needs. If you do not want information collected through the use of Cookies, there is a simple procedure in most browsers that allows you to deny or accept the Cookie feature. However, you should note that Cookies may be necessary to provide you with some features of our on-line services.

### 7 Links to other sites

7.1 We provide links to web sites outside of our web site, as well as to third party web sites. These linked sites are not under our control, and we cannot accept responsibility for the conduct of companies linked to our web site. Before disclosing your personal information on any other web site, we advise you to examine the terms and conditions of using that web site and its privacy statement.

### 8 Problems or questions

8.1 If we become aware of any ongoing concerns or problems with our web site, we will take these issues seriously and work to address these concerns. If you have any further queries relating to our Privacy Policy, or you have a problem or complaint, please contact us.

### 9 Further data protection information

9.1 For more information about data protection issues in the United Kingdom and protecting your privacy, visit the website of the Information Commissioner's office at www.ico.gov.uk.
